Good afternoon. Gil here from the TRT
and hormone optimization group. As you
all may know, myself and Stephen Davos
and all of the other moderators and
many, many providers in our group have
spent close to a decade now trying to
help and educate men on hormone
replacement therapy, proper protocols,
uh proper science, and how to achieve
optimal results. We've all done this
essentially on our own time uh just for
the sake of trying to improve the
industry and improve uh men's health
overall. And um unfortunately yesterday
Facebook decided that our group violated
some policies. They won't tell us which
policies, but they went ahead and they
shut the group down uh with no warning.
We appealed it and they denied our
appeal, claiming that we are in
violation of their guidelines. Again, we
don't know what was done wrong. I
personally have been very adamant over
the years at preventing specific
discussions related to anabolic steroid
use or other illicit drugs uh because I
feared that that would be looked on
negatively by the regulatory divisions
of whatever social media platforms are
out there. Um and I don't know if that
was the case. We don't know what
happened. We do know that the group is
currently shut down or suspended. What
we did is we went ahead because we've
had a lot of people reach out asking
where the group went, thinking maybe
they were banned, which was not the
case. Uh so we went ahead and we started
from scratch. We had about almost 18,000
active members in the group and uh we
went ahead and we started a new one uh
today from scratch because we feel that
there's still a lot of people out there
that need the help. Uh so we encourage
you to click the link here in the
description and join the new group. Yes,
it's a lot of work. Yes, we're in for
the run. uh to do this again and to try
to help as many people as we can. So, we
encourage you, click the link, join the
new group, uh share it with your
friends, bring anyone you know who may
be interested in the topic or perhaps
was in the previous group over to the
new group, and we'll just keep it going
as we always have. Thanks, and we'll see
you on the other side.